http://www.hotmixx.com/privacy.php?osCsid=o0bpn07vtf9l6j4imi62kptq83

Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Lxtasy Sounds at Hotmixx.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
How policy changes will be communicated.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. Information collected from you includes your name, address, email address, phone number, ip address, and credit card information when applicable.
We do not store any credit card information in our databases.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Changes to this Policy
We may make changes to this privacy notice from time to time. You may check back on this page at any time to see our current policy.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800-757-0769 or via email at sales@hotmixx.com.
Continue
DJs
Please SelectBig Oomp Record..Break BanditsDeviousDexterityDJ 007DJ ArsonDJ B-NastyDJ BlazeDJ Charlie Chan..DJ ChillwillDJ DDJ Danny DeeDJ Danny SDJ Dirty HarryDJ E-KimDJ E-LijahDJ EnochDJ FinesseDJ FlexDJ FlowDJ Fly TyDJ GeraDJ J-Boogie & D..DJ JamshaDJ Jazzy Jeff &..DJ JellyDJ JuiceDJ JukeboxDJ Kid CapriDJ Krazee RaeDJ KSmoothDJ LeeDJ MessiahDJ Mister CeeDJ Paul BunyonDJ PowerDJ Ray RozayDJ RectangleDJ RevolutionDJ Rob E RobDJ RondonDJ RuckusDJ ScratchezDJ Sin-ceroDJ SloMotionDJ SpinatikDJ SupremeDJ Ty BoogieDJ White RockDJ-Marc EdwardsGreg StreetLil HenryOtaku GangVarious ArtistsXay The DJ
Genre
Big Oomp SprayBluesClub/HouseDJ Jelly ThrowbacksFeatured ArtistGospelHip-HopJazzOld School Hip-HopOld School R&BR&BReggaeSlow Jam MixSpecialty CDsDVDs
Specials
Futuristic
ShawtyRATED R * Continuous...$4.99$3.99Street Runnaz 98RATED R***** Souds o...$4.99$1.99Flex On Em 2 (DVD)RATED R * Video Remi...$9.99$5.99The ReturnRATED R
***** Mixed...$4.99$3.99DJ D vol. 11RATED R
***** Conti...$4.99$2.99
Shopping Cart
0 items
Bestsellers
NY Is In Da HouseTake OffATL HoeCereal KillerWay Back Wednesday Session 60I Am The Cookout 2020 pt 2Juke Joint 2It's My Turn vol. 3Summertime 2020Blendz 4 Ever 6
Reviews
Classic mixes by the masters Dj jelly and Mc Assault...
Wish List
Your Wish List is empty.
